Brandon Hickman

Denver, CO, 80231 | 720-421-0875 | branhickman@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio url (TBD)

WEB DEVELOPER

- Experienced leader that has succeeded in fast-paced B2B environments and grew a startup from \$400k in revenue to over \$8MM.
- Quick to learn new things and has a passion for technology and finding new and innovative ways to solve problems.
- Highly organized and thoughtful about how development work is completed, a holdover from my time being responsible for all company operations in my previous roles.

TECHNICAL & INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Mongo, JSON, Typescript, EJS, DTL

Libraries and Frameworks: React, Express.js, Django, Jquery, Bootstrap, Semantic UI, Bulma

Databases and other: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, RESTful Routing, JSON API

Interpersonal skills: Executive Communication, Project Management, Customer Service

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Sharmagotchi - GitHub | App | Javascript, HTML, CSS

An intuitive pet simulator that takes all the responsibilities that owning a pet entails and turns them into an enjoyable and quirky 8-bit gaming experience.

- Created a web app with a mobile first approach using only javascript, html, and css.
- Implemented functionality that mimics real life pet tasks in a way that's enjoyable and engaging.
- Received glowing code reviews regarding app structure, function and game logic.

MORE PROJECTS ARE TBD PENDING COURSE

App Name - GitHub | App - Coding language used | Coding language used

One sentence about what the app does, think of this like a one-line marketing pitch

- Bullet points that describe the features you created in your app. Use the formula:
- Action verb + what you did + result
- Action verb + what you did + result

EXPERIENCE

Interfaith Bridge, Web Developer

Denver, CO, 04/2022 - Current

- Manage and oversee web development efforts. Including planning, coding, and implementing new or improved functionality within interfaithbridge.com to increase engagement, brand perception, and ability to bring in new patients.
- Launched a completely overhauled website, eliminated the need for squarespace, and reduced operational overhead by 90%
- Implemented an ecommerce webstore that generates passive income based on proprietary therapy resources developed by Interfaith Bridge that has led to over a 10% increase in annual revenue.

Flowhub, VP of People Operations

Denver, CO, 02/2017 - 04/2022

- Coordinate HR and People Operations for all departments, advise CEO, run point on strategic initiatives, plan and direct
 administrative, financial, and operational activities, provide oversight and guidance to executive staff, and oversee general
 policies and procedures.
- In an executive capacity I directly contributed to 19x revenue growth over the course of my tenure.
- Implemented performance management system and raised overall performance scores by over 30%.
- Created a framework to run the company remotely in 2020 and lowered annual operational costs by just over 1MM by eliminating unnecessary physical spaces, restructuring company meetings and communication, and updating essential roles.

Atpo, Director of Customer Solutions

Denver, CO, 09/2015 - 02/2017

- Led a team of solutions consultants that managed customer inquiries and technical issues, implemented Apto software with customer base, and maintained customer service level agreements.
- Increased customer NPS scores by 30% over the course of my tenure
- Reduced time to onboard new clients by over 50% by replacing general implementation workflow with a customer journey that delegated onboarding milestones to sales reps, implementation reps, support reps, and customer success reps.

EDUCATION

General AssemblyRemote, Certificate Expected: MM/YYYY

Full-stack software engineering 420+ hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies.